Come, sorrow.We welcome thee.
来吧，悲伤，我们欢迎你
Let us join in grief,
让我们一起感受不幸
rejoice in despair,
绝望让我们欣喜
and honor the fortunate dead.
为侥幸的死亡而荣耀
Dearly beloved...
亲爱的
Good show, old man.
表现的不错，老家伙
Gomez.
Cara mia?
Marvelous news.
美妙的惊喜
I'm going to have a baby...
我要生孩子了
right now.
就现在
Nurse, how close are the contractions?
护士，宫缩频率是多少？
Every 15 seconds, Doctor.
每15秒，医生
Are you in unbearable pain?
你现在是否处于无法忍受的痛苦？
Is it inhuman? My darling, is it torture?
残酷吗？亲爱的，是否备受折磨？
Oui.
And then mommy kissed daddy,
然后妈咪亲吻爸爸
and the angel told the stork.
然后天使告诉鹳鸟
The stork flew down from heaven
鹳鸟从天堂降临
and left a diamond under a leaf in the cabbage patch,
留下一颗钻石在布袋里的叶子下面
and the diamond turned into a baby.
然后钻石变成了一个宝宝
Our parents are having a baby, too.
我们的父母也有宝宝了
They had sex.
他们做爱了
Push, Mrs. Addams.
用力，亚当斯夫人
Forceps!
镊子！
Forceps.
Forceps!
镊子！
Aah!
Would you like anesthesia?
你需要麻醉嘛？
No, thank you. But ask the children.
不，谢谢，不过你可以问问孩子
Cara mia.
Mon cher.
Mrs. Addams, the baby?
亚当斯夫人，孩子？
Pardon.
原谅我
- It's a boy. - It's a girl.
-那是男孩 -那是女孩
- Gomez! - What news?
怎么样了？
Father, what is it?
爸爸，怎么样了？
It's an Addams!
那是一个亚当斯！
I've arranged a little surprise,my dearest.
我安排了一个小小的惊喜，我最亲爱的
I hope you like it.
我希望你喜欢
Oh, Gomez, it's dark,it's depressing, it's desolate.
哦Gomez，它是多么黑暗，阴沉，凄凉
It says, "toddler."
这是婴儿房
It's a dream.
这是一个梦
Come, cara mia.
来吧cara mia
The Addams cradle.
这是小亚当斯的摇篮
Welcome home, my son.
欢迎回家，我的儿子
That's not true.
这不是真的
Everyone knows it is.
所有人都知道
When you have a new baby,one of the other children has to die.
当你有了一个新的孩子，其余中的一个必须死
- Really?- It's a tradition. One of us has to go.
-真的？-这是传统，我们中的一个必须死
Which one?
哪一个？
Well, they only need one boy.
他们只需要一个男孩子
He has my father's eyes.
他有我父亲的眼睛
Gomez, take those out of his mouth.
Gomez,把那些东西从他嘴里拿走
Coochie coochie coo.
A baby in the house.
一个宝宝在这个房子里
It's about time. Hey, kiddo.
这是 时间问题，嘿，老兄
Did you see that?
你看到了嘛?
He's a real devil.
他是真正的魔鬼
Pugsley, the baby weighs 10 pounds.
Pugsley，孩子重10磅
The cannonball weighs 20 pounds.
炮弹重20磅
Which will hit the stone walkway first?
哪个会先砸到石廊？
I'm still on fractions.
不知道
Which do you think?
你觉得是哪个?
The cannonball?
炮弹？
Very good. But which one will bounce?
但是哪个会弹回来？
The baby?
孩子？
There's only one way to find out.
只有一个方法可以知道
Ready?
准备？
1...
2...
3.
What a glorious evening.
多么美好的夜晚
Rain.
下雨
Cara mia.
Oh, dear.
哦，亲爱的
Children,why do you hate the baby?
孩子们，你们为什么讨厌宝宝？
We just want to play with him.
我们只想跟他玩
Especially his head.
特别是他的头
Do you think we love the baby more than you?
你们是不是认为我们爱宝宝多过爱你们？
- Yes.- Yes.
是的
Do you think when a new baby arrives,
你们是不是认为当一个新的宝宝来到这里
another child has to die?
另一个就必须死？
- Yes.- Yes.
是的
Well,that's just not true.
好，那不是真的
Not anymore.
不再是了
It's just sibling rivalry.
这只是兄弟间的竞争
Gomez, do you remember what we were like?
Gomez，你还记得我们是怎么样的吗？
- I hated you!- I despised you.
-我讨厌你！-我鄙视你！
I choked him till he lost consciousness
我把他掐昏
and had to be put on a respirator.
必须急救为止
I tied him to a tree
我把他绑在树上
and pulled out four of his permanent teeth.
拔了他四个牙
When he was asleep,
当他睡觉的时候
I opened his skull and removed his brains.
敲开他的头把他的脑子取出来
You did?
你做过？
A brother!
兄弟！
Brother!
Children, you see?
孩子们，看到了嘛？
"Death! Death to the enemies
把死亡带给敌人
of the people of the republic."
为了人民 为了共和国
Hoorah!
Justice is served.
正义得到了声张
Bring forward the evil one.
把罪犯带上来
[La Marseillaise Plays]
马赛曲选段
You have betrayed the people of France.
你背叛了法国人民
You are evil incarnate.
你是罪恶的化身
How do you plead?
你如何辩护
[Pugsley] Guilty.
有罪
Guilty by her own admission.
有罪，她自己承认了
The sentence is death.
判决处死
Executioner,place her on the block.
侩子手，把他放到闸刀上
1...
2...
Children,what are you doing?
孩子们，你们在干什么？
- Playing!- Playing!
玩！
3!
Woe to the republic.
国家的不幸
Look at you.
看看你
Midnight, moonlight,
午夜，月光
surrounded by death.
被死亡环绕
It's been too long.
太久了
Do it!
Hold him still!
动手！扶住他！
[Gunshot,Glass Breaking]
You missed.
你射偏了！
Here, catch!
这里，抓着！
I don't want him!
我不要他
One house,three children.
一座房子，三个孩子
So many windows.
那么多窗子
My darling, it's you I'm worried about,
我亲爱的，我很担心你
the stress,all this squabbling.
压力和争吵
Oh, I'll be fine.
哦，我还好
I'm just like any modern woman,trying to have it all--
我觉得现代点的女性应该可以解决
loving husband, a family.
丈夫，家庭
It's just I wish I had more time
我希望我有更多时间
to seek out the dark forces
寻找出黑暗的力量
and join their hellish crusade,that's all.
参加他们地狱一般的战争，就这样
You can! You shall!So it must be!
你可以这么做！就应该这么做！
But how?
但是要如何？
Children,as your new nanny,
孩子们，作为你们的新保姆
I know that we're all concerned
我知道我们都关心
about the environment,
环境
so this morning, let's discuss
所以今天早晨，我们来谈谈
how to prevent forest fires.
如何预防森林火灾
Prevent them?
预防？
All right, children,
好，孩子们
I've had it up to here.
这样
Now you just answer one simple question.
现在，你们回到一个简单的问题
Where is that baby?
孩子在哪里？
Which part?
哪个部分？
Hello, kiddies.
你们好，孩子们
I'm Polly the puppet.
我是木偶波利
What shall we do today?
我们今天应该做什么呢？
I know. Let's all clean our rooms.
我知道，让我们来打扫房间
Hello, Polly.
你好，波利
I'll clean my room
我已经打扫了我的房间
in exchange for your immortal soul.
为了交换你不朽的灵魂
Hi. Addams residence?
嗨，这里的亚当斯家嘛？
Ooh, it's old.
哦，真古老
And big.
也很大
Lurch.
摇摇欲坠
Hi! Hi. I'm Debbie Jellinsky from the agency.
嗨，我是Debbie Jellinsky 从代理商那里来
The agency?
代理？
But they claimed no one else was available.
但是他们说没人有空
They suggested a Doberman.
他们建议雇佣一条猎狗
Surprise!I've been out of town.
惊喜，我刚从镇上回来
Are you the mom?
你是妈妈？
I am Mrs. Addams.
我是亚当斯夫人
I love your dress.It's so tight.
我喜欢你的裙子 很紧身
Thank you.
谢谢
Gomez.
I believe we may have a new nanny...
我觉得我们有了一个新的保姆
Miss Jellinsky.
Jellinsky小姐
Deb.
Isn't he a lady-killer?
他是位女性杀手嘛？
Acquitted.
应该还不是
I'll show you all my references
我会解释有关我的一切
so you'll know I'm not a homicidal maniac.
你会知道我不是杀人狂
- Of course you're not.- You're too young.
当然你不是，你这么年轻
Welcome to our home.
欢迎来我们家
There's a belfry,a swamp,
一个钟楼，一片沼泽
and a dungeon down below.
一条龙在下面
- Cable?- Of course.
-锁起来了？-当然
Debbie.
Oh, is that the little critter?
哦，就是这个小畜牲？
Oh, no. This is our baby.
哦，不，这个是我们的宝宝
He's adorable. He's perfect. What's his name?
真可爱，他叫什么名字？
It was agony.
非常苦恼
We went through all the usual baby names...
我们试过了所有普通孩子的名字
Lucifer...
Benito...
Mao.
Then we came to our senses,
最后我们又来灵感
something a child could live with...
一个适合孩子的
Pubert.
Pubert...
I like it.
我喜欢他
It's filthy.
真恶心
May I?
可以吗？
Your dress,is it flammable?
你的裙子易燃嘛？
You've had your shots--
你注射疫苗了吗？
measles, mumps, rabies?
麻疹，腮腺炎，狂犬病
Oh, I just adore little babies.
哦，我喜欢这个小家伙
I just want to squeeze them till there's not a breath left
我想捏的他喘不过气来
in their tiny little bodies.
在他们的小身体上
Hello, Pubert.
你好Pubert
I love you.
我爱你
[Knock On Door]敲门声
Children, this is Miss Jellinsky,our new nanny.
孩子们，这个是Jellinsky小姐，你们的新保姆
What do we say?
我们应该说什么？
Be afraid.Be very afraid.
害怕，非常害怕
Look at you--
你们看
all cooped up in this house with a new baby.
在这个房子里和一个新生儿在一起
That's not easy,is it?
不容易，不是嘛？
No.
不是
Why, I bet sometimes
我打赌
you wish it was still just the two of you.
你们还是希望这里就只有你们两个
Or less.
或者更少
Well, don't you worry.
你们不用担心
Everything's going to be just fine.
一切都会好的
I love them.
我爱他们
Thing...
东西
stop that.
停下
He likes you.
他喜欢你
Heh heh heh heh.
I'm good with my hands.
我对我的手很好
What a wonderful family,
多美的一家人啊
although there's one fella I haven't met yet.
虽然有一位我还不认识
Hi there, mister.
你好先生
Your nephew?
你侄子？
My brother.
我兄弟
No!
不
Fester,come out here.
Fester，到这里来
He's very shy.
他真害羞
Fester, this is Miss Jellinsky,our new nanny.
这是我们的新保姆
Hello, Fester.
你好
These Addams men,where do you find them?
这些亚当斯的男人你怎么找到的？
It has to be damp.
有点潮湿
I can't wait.
我等不及了
I'll start first thing tomorrow.
我明天就会开始工作
Why not tonight?
为什么不今晚
[Morticia]Good night, Debbie.
晚安，Debbie
Good night!
晚安
Scream if you need anything.
假如你有任何需要就尖叫
So we've hired Miss Jellinsky.
我们就雇佣Jellinsky小姐吧
She's a gem, don't you think?
她是一块宝石，你不这么认为嘛？
She's perfect.
她很完美
Oh, Fester, I'm such a lucky man.
Fester，我是一个多么幸运的男人
I hope that someday you'll know the indescribable joy
我希望有一天你能知道这难以言语的快乐
of having children
有孩子
and of paying someone else to raise them.
为抚养他们长大的人付钱
First wouldn't I have to get married?
首先我不是应该先结婚嘛？
You're just a boy. There's plenty of time.
你还是个孩子，需要时间
You'll meet someone,someone very special,
你会遇到一个很特别的人
someone who won't press charges.
一个不计付出的人
Oh, I'd like that.
我喜欢
You rascal.
你个小无赖
Oh, and what's this?
这是什么
- Mom.
妈呀
Tonight on America's Most Disgusting Unsolved Crimes,
今晚，在最恶心的悬案中
we investigate the case of Ursula...
我们来研究Ursula
Carmen...
and Nadine--
和Nadine
three very different women with one thing in common--
三个不同的女人的一个共同点
murder!谋杀！
And they're all the same woman.
她们是同一个人
She's known by the police as the Black Widow.
警察叫她黑寡妇
She mates, then she kills.
她寻找情人，她杀人
She investigates wealthy men,
她寻找富有的男子
finding the richest, loneliest bachelors,
寻找最富有，最孤独的未婚男子
gaining their trust and their love,
给他们信任和爱
and finally,she marries them.
最和他们结婚
Then, on the wedding night,she kills them.
在新婚之夜杀了他们
The deaths appear accidental.
死亡发生的很偶然
After the funeral,she disappears, cash in hand,
葬礼以后，她拿着钱消失了
but the money never lasts.
但是钱不能永远够花
Soon the Black Widow is hungry again,
很快黑寡妇又饿了
hungry for cash,hungry for love.
渴望金钱和爱
A mistress of disguise,she's eluded the authorities for years.
善于伪装，逃避了有关当局多年的追捕
Who is she,
她是谁
and what seemingly innocent pose will she next assume?
她会再次设定什么样的看似清白的背景
All we can say is...
我们能说的是
bachelors, beware.
未婚男子，小心
We'll be going out for most of the morning.
我们大部分早晨都要出门
All the important numbers--
所有重要的电话号码
police, fire department,morgue.
警局，消防所，停尸房
Fester, come along.
Fester，过来
Goodbye, Fester.
再见，Fester
Say goodbye to Debbie.
跟debbie说再见
Have fun!
开心点
Mmm-mmm-mmm-mmm!
Fester Addams. My, my.
Fester Addams，我的天那
Stocks and bonds...
股份和抵押
deeds...
契据
gold bullion.
金条
Treasury bills...
国库券
IRAs.
个人退休帐户
What a strange old house.
多么奇怪的老房子
It's so drafty.
通风真好
It's really no place for children.
这里真是孩子们的好地方
No place at all.
没其他更好的了
Hold still,you little brat.
别动，你这个小捣蛋鬼
He's not a brat.
他不捣蛋鬼
Of course not.He's an adorable little baby.
当然不是，他是可爱的小宝宝
Fine. Rub it in.
好，把他擦干净
We're getting him all ready
他应经准备好看
for a nice little walk.
去散个小步
Would you like to come?
你来嘛？
Are you really a nanny?
你真的是个保姆嘛？
What a question.
这算什么问题
Why did you come here?
你为什么来这里？
Why, to take care of you...
我来照顾你们啊
all of you.
你们所有
Especially my uncle?
特别是我叔叔？
I shouldn't be telling you this.
我不应该告诉你们这个
They swore me to secrecy,
他们要我发誓保密
the little angels,
小天使们
but they want to go.
但是他们想去
It's all they talked about all morning.
他们一个早上都在谈论这个
They're just afraid to ask you.
他们害怕问你们
They're afraid you'll think they don't love you.
他们害怕你们以为他们不爱你们了
The poor things.
可怜的小东西
It's a bizarre request.
这是个奇怪的要求
It's horrifying.
这很可怕
They have their hearts set on it.
他们全心全意
I knew you'd want to know
我知道你们想知道
as concerned, caring parents.
做体贴的父母
Oh, Gomez,what shall we do?
我们应该做什么？
How can we say no?
我们如何说不？
Don't even mention it.
不要提及这个
Just do it.
直接去做
I'm sure they'll deny everything,
我保证他们会否认一切
but they want to go,
但是他们想去
God love them.
上帝爱他们
- Summer camp.- Summer camp.
夏令营
"Camp Chippewa."
Chippewa夏令营
How charming.
多么迷人
What's a chippewa?
什么是chippewa
It's an old Indian word.
那是古老的印第安世界
It means orphan.
它的意思是孤儿院
Fresh air...
新鲜空气
the scent of pine.
松木的气味
[Morticia] Wednesday, look at all of the other children--
星期三，看看其他孩子
their freckles, their bright little eyes,
他们的雀斑，他们明亮的小眼睛
their eager,friendly smiles.
他们渴望的友好的微笑
Help them.救救他们
Hi. I'm Amanda Buckman.
嗨，我是Amanda Buckman
Why are you dressed like that?
你为什么穿成这样？
Like what?
什么样？
Like you're going to a funeral.
就像你要去参加葬礼
Why are you dressed like somebody died?
你为什么穿的像有人死了？
Wait.
我在等
Hi. Don Buckman.
嗨Don Buckman
Isn't this place something else?
这里没点其他的嘛？
Very exclusive.
非常独特
A kid has to be extra special to get in,
一个孩子必须非常特别才能参加
gifted, exceptional.
天赋异禀
Our Amanda's already skipped two grades.
我们Amanda已经跳了两级
How about your boy?
你们的孩子呢？
Probation.
实习
We just love Chippewa.
我们爱Chippewa
Amanda couldn't wait.
Amanda等不及了
It's all she talked about.
她一直在说这个
She's got a whole new wardrobe.
她带了全部的新衣服
And this little lady?
这位年轻的女士呢？
Wednesday's at that very special age
星期三处在一个很特别的年龄段
when a girl has only one thing on her mind.
那时候女孩在她脑子里只有一个念头
Boys?
男孩子？
Homicide.
杀人犯
Attention!
注意！
Hey! Listen up,everybody.
大家听好！
I'm Gary Granger!
我是Gary Granger！
And I'm Becky Martin-Granger.
我是Becky Martin-Granger！
We're the owners and directors here at Camp Chippewa,
我们是夏令营的主管
America's foremost facility for...
美国最早的技能
privileged young adults.
为幸运的小大人们准备
And we're all here to learn, to grow,
我们在这里学习，长大
and to just plain have fun!
娱乐！
'Cause that's what being privileged is all about.
那是我们感到幸运的原因
Buffy!
How are you?
你好吗？
I'm fine.How are you?
我很好你呢？
How are you doing?
你怎么样？
I don't think I like it here.
我不觉得我喜欢这里
Do you know how dirty you are?
你知道你有多脏嘛？
Please leave him alone.
请让他一个人呆着
I can't breathe.
我不能呼吸了
Stand up straight,please.
站直
This is why he's always sick.
这就是为什么他老生病
Don't start with me.
不要盯着我
This has nothing to do with allergies.
我们又没什么办法对付过敏
You did this.
是你干的
Can you breathe?
你能呼吸嘛？
Stand up straight.Stand up straight.
站直站直
"Everyone at the ball
每个人都在舞会上
"turned and stared at Cinderella.
盯着灰姑娘
"Who is that beautiful woman?everyone asked.
这个漂亮的女孩是谁？所有人都在问
"Even Prince Charming noticed the new arrival.
连王子也注意到了这个新到的
"Who are you?he asked Cinderella.
你是谁，王子问
"My name is Cinderella,she said to the prince.
我叫灰姑娘，她告诉王子
"Could you tell me
你能告诉我
"who is that man over by the punch bowl,
那拿大酒杯的男人是谁
"that fascinating man,
那个迷人的男子
"that oddly sensual man,
那个奇怪的男人
"that man who makes me quiver under my bodice,
这个男人让我颤抖
that bald man?"
那个秃头的男人
She's driving me wild!
她让我疯狂
Who?
谁？
Debbie.
Even the sound of her name...
连她名字的声音
Debbie.
Isn't it beautiful?
这不美吗？
She makes me think of vinyl.Chemicals!
她让我想到炼金术师！
Truly, Fester,
的确Fester
has it finally happened,at long last?
这么久以来它终于发生了？
I don't know.I think so.
我不知道，我想是的
All these years I've watched you and Morticia
这些年，我看着你和Morticia
through windows,doorways,
隔着窗子，门口
keyholes.
锁孔
I've been so happy for you,
我很为你高兴
but I have to confess I've been jealous, too.
但是我必须承认我也很妒忌
I've dreamed that sometime
我有时也梦想过这些
there might be someone for me.
有一个人属于我
There's Thing.
这里有“东西”
I know, but I want more--
我知道，但我需要更多
legs, elbows,
腿，手肘
a head.
一个头
Two legs?
两条腿？
Dare I ask Debbie to dinner?
我能邀请Debbie吃晚餐嘛？
What if she says no?
假如她说不怎么办？
What if she says yes?
假如她说好怎么办？
If I asked her,would you come,
假如我邀请她你会来嘛？
you and Morticia?
你和Morticia
Of course.
当然
Life saving.
救生训练
We're all
top-notch swimmers.
顶级的游泳运动员
Now we show our stuff
现在我们展示我们的学识
and earn those certificates.
获得一张证书
How about our first little pair
我们的第一对
of life saving buddies?
救生搭档？
Amanda, Wednesday.
Is that your bathing suit?
这是你的泳衣？
Is that your over bite?
你不觉得太紧吗？
One of you will be the drowning victim.
你们中的一个将是溺水者
The other one will be our lifesaver.
另一个是我们的救生员
I'll be the victim.
我当溺水者
All your life.
你这辈子
I'm going to be an actress.
我要当一名演员
Brava!
很好！
Now jump in,swim out a few yards,
跳进去，游几码
and start drowning.
然后开始溺水
Help me!
救命！
I'm drowning!
我溺水了！
Help me!
救命
I'm dying!
我就要死了！
I can't swim.
我不会游泳
It's our favorite bistro.
这是我最喜欢的餐厅
We've been coming here for years.
我们多年都来这里
Of course,it has been redone.
当然，这里改装过
Oh, it's just...
哦，这里……
lovely.
真可爱
Isn't it, Fester?
不是吗？Fester
Fester.
It's a quaint French custom--
这是有趣的法国传统
sharing half-eaten bread.
分享咬了一半的面包
Fester is truly continental.
Fester是真正的欧洲人
He spent many years abroad.
他在国外呆了很多年
He speaks 12 languages fluently.
他能流利的说12种语言
I could tell.
我能分辨出来
When I first saw him,
我第一次看到他
I thought he was from Europe.
我觉得他来自欧洲
You did?
真的？
It's true.
是啊
But I took a bath.
但是我只是去了一下浴室洗澡
Fester's really a wonderful man.
Fester真的是个好人
He's just terribly shy.
他只是非常害羞
I just can't tell--
我知道
does he like me at all?
他喜欢我吗？
Of course he does.
当然
He vomited.
他吐了
Does he always do that with women he likes?
他对喜欢的女人都这样吗？
Oh, no.
哦，不
Just you.
只有你
Ah.
Do you think she minded?
你觉得她介意吗？
Of course not.
当然不
She adores you.
她崇拜你
I'm making such a mess of things.
我把事情搞的一团糟
Gomez, how do you do it?
Gomez，你是怎么做到的？
How can I be like you?
我要怎么样才能像你？
How can I be suave?
我要怎样才能文雅受人喜爱？
Woo her, admire her,
欣赏她，向她求爱
make her feel like she's the most sublime creature on Earth.
让她觉得她是地球上最完美的创造
Yes. That's it?
是啊，这样？
We're back,
我们回来
noses powdered.
补妆
Perfection achieved.
完美着陆
We are the luckiest brothers on Earth.
我们是世界上最幸运的兄弟
We are unworthy of such splendor,
我们配不起如此美妙的造物
undeserving of such radiance.
不配如此的光辉
Uh, that's right.
是啊
We should have...ugly girls.
我们应该去找……难看的女孩
And then the ghost said,
然后幽灵说
"And I will haunt you forever."
我会永远缠着你
- Ooh.
Wednesday,
星期三
you have to continue the ghost story.
你要接着说鬼故事
This is dumb.
这很愚蠢
Well, if you can't do it...
假如你讲不了……
And, so, the next night,
然后，第二天晚上
the ghost returned to the haunted cabin,
幽灵回到了小屋
and he said to the campers,
对野营者们说
"None of you really believe in me,
你们都不相信我
so I'll have to prove my power."
我要加强我的力量
And the next morning,
第二天早上
when the campers woke up,
当野营者们醒来
all of their old noses had grown back.
他们所有旧的鼻子都长回来了
- Aah!
Oh, Fester,
how you must hate me.
你一定很讨厌我
What?
什么？
Here you are,
你在这里
a debonair man of the world.
全世界最温文尔雅的男人
How I must bore you.
我一定让你觉得很无聊
Oh, never.
哦，从来没有
Fester, before we go any further,
Fester，在我们更进一步之前
I have a confession,
我必须承认
something I must tell you.
我要告诉你
I'm a virgin.
我是个处女
You are?
真的？
Yes.
是啊
What's that?
什么是处女？
It--It's someone
那是
who's never experienced physical love.
从未体验过身体爱情的人
Oh.
哦
You mean,with another person.
你是说跟另一个人
Then, Debbie,
那么Debbie
I have a confession to make, as well.
我也必须告诉你
I'm one, too.
我也是
You? You?
你？你？
Yes.
是啊
But with your looks,your charm,
但是你的外貌，你的魅力
women must follow you everywhere.
女人们肯定导出跟着你
Store detectives.
商店售货员
Oh, Fester,
I always dreamed
我一直梦想
of meeting someone untouched,
遇到一个从没被碰过的人
someone pure,
纯洁的
someone...just like you.
就像你一样
You'll meet him.
你会找到的
And--And I dreamed that when I met him,
我梦想着当我遇到他的时候
that we would wait until our wedding night
我们可以等到我们的新婚之夜
to give ourselves to one another,
吧我们自己给另一个人
to make the ultimate sacrifice.
作出最后的牺牲
A goat?
一个替罪羊？
Until now I thought it was impossible,
知道现在我认为还不可能
but, Fester Addams,
但是Fester Addams
I love you.
我爱你
You do?
真的？
Please, I have to know how you feel about me.
我想知道你对我的感觉
I love you.
我爱你
I worship you.
我崇拜你
I'd do anything for you.
我愿意为你做任何事
I'd pay.
我付了帐
Fester!
Debbie!
Oh.
Look at him.
看看他
So peaceful.
那么平静
This evening as I watched Fester and Debbie,
今晚当我看到Fester和Debbie
I kept my fingers crossed.
我交叉起了手指
I hoped...
我希望……
I prayed.
我祈祷
Let them fall in love.
让他们坠入爱河
Let them know happiness.
让他们了解快乐
Let them adopt.
让他们相互依偎
Gomez, Morticia,
great news--
天大的好消息
Something impossible,a miracle.
不可能的奇迹！
- The rash...- It's gone.
疹子……退了
I'm engaged.
我订婚了
That ring...
那个戒指……
It was our mother's.She was buried with it.
那是我们母亲的戒指，和她一起埋起来了
Mail call.
邮件
Addams.
亚当斯
Barkley,
Castleman, Calloway,
Dexter, Donman,
Edwards, Evans,
Finley, Fisher,
Framingham...
Oh, no.
哦，不
What is it?
怎么了？
This is unspeakable.
无法形容
Is something wrong?Bad news?
有什么不对嘛？坏事？
It's the worst thing ever in the history of human events.
这是人类历史上最坏的事情
Uncle Fester is getting married.
Fester叔叔要结婚了
A wedding?
婚礼？
But that's great news.
但那是好事
To whom?
和谁
The nanny.
保姆
Get out of the cabin.
从屋里出去
I'd kill myself.
我会自杀的
The help?
帮帮忙
I'm sure she's a very nice lady.
我相信她是一位很好的女士
I think that's disgusting.
我觉得那令人作呕
Their whole family's
他们一家
like some weird medical experiment.
就像一个奇怪的药物试验
I think they're like circus people.
我觉得他们是马戏团的
What did you say?
你说什么？
Tempers.
脾气
Group hug.
集体拥抱
Wednesday.
Pugsley.
Will a hug hurt us?
拥抱会伤害我们嘛？
We don't hug.
我们不拥抱
Oh, they're just shy.
他们只是害羞
We're not shy.
我们不害羞
We're contagious.
我们带接触传染
I'm sensing some friction here,
我感觉这里有点摩擦
something not quite Chippewa.
有点不那么和谐
- Mm-hmm.
Hey, no problem-o.
没问题
All they need are good friends, good fun,
他们只是需要好朋友，娱乐
and a little time in the harmony hut.
一点时间在温馨的小屋里
How long do we have to stay in here?
我们要在这里呆多久？
Until we crack.
知道我们爆炸
Have fun.
开心下
What are you in for?
你为什么在这里？
I wouldn't go horseback riding.
我不要骑马
That's all?
就这样？
And I wouldn't make a bird house.
我不要做鸟房
Why not?
为什么不？
I just wanted to read.
我只想读书
Not on my time, four-eyes.
不是在这个时间，四眼
Aah!
Aah aah aah!
Hurry up.
快点
I'm coming.
我来了
Wait.
等下
Be careful.
小心
Tetanus.
破伤风
There they are!
他们在那里
I saw them sneak out.
我看到他们溜出去了
What do you think you're doing?
你们觉得你们在干嘛？
We have to see our family.
我们要回家看看
It's important.
这很重要
More important than summer fun?
比夏令营还重要？
More important than making new friends?
比交朋友还重要？
More important than sharing?
比分享还重要？
Joel Glicker,I'm surprised at you.
Joel Glicker，我感到很惊讶看到你
I have to get out of here.
我必须出去
I have allergies
我过敏
Oh, you're allergic?
你过敏嘛？
To sunshine,archery, and crafts?
阳光，射击，工艺？
Yes.
是的
I think they should be punished.
我觉得他们必须受到惩罚
Punished! Punished!
惩罚！惩罚！
No! We are not here to punish.
我们不是到这里来惩罚的
We are here to inspire.
我们是来受鼓舞的
Know what our little ninja friends need?
知道我们的小忍者朋友需要什么？
Know what might turn their sad, wasted lives around?
知道什么能驱赶他们的悲伤
What?
什么？
~ Kumbaya, my Lord ~
~ Kumbaya ~
~ Oh, Lord, Kumbaya ~~
Now, Debbie,have you met everyone?
Debbie你见过所有人了嘛？
Morticia.
Margaret.
Margaret, this is our bride-to-be.
Margaret，这是我们的准新娘
Welcome to our family.
欢迎来我们家
I can't tell you what it's meant
我不知道这么跟你说
joining the Addams clan.
加入亚当斯一族
Have you met my husband Cousin Itt?
你见过我丈夫Cousin Itt了嘛？
Cousin Itt?
We've been so happy,
我们非常快乐
and, just as little Pubert arrived,
小Pubert降临了的时候
we were blessed with our own little bundle of joy.
上帝保佑我们也得到了自己的宝贝
What?
什么
Oh, I didn't say anything.
哦，我没说什么
That's the baby's nickname-- What?
这是孩子的绰号-“什么”
From the obstetrician.
产科医生取的
Isn't he precious?
他不可爱么？
We've had offers.
我们有提供者
~ For he's
a jolly good fellow ~
~ Which nobody
can deny ~~
You guys are the best bunch of friends
你们这些家伙是最好的朋友
a fella could hope for.
值得信任的男人
What a party!
多美妙的聚会！
And now for the piece de resistance.
现在是主菜
Ta-da!
That poor girl.
可怜的女孩
Lurch, was she in there before you baked?
Lurch，你烤之前她就在里面了嘛？
So, so, so.
C'est la vie.
这就是生活！
Ha ha ha ha!
Are you really allergic?
你真的过敏？
Uh-huh.
To almost everything.
几乎所有东西
No, you're not.
不， 你没有
Am, too.
我有
I can't have dairy products
我不能吃乳制品
or wear wool
羊毛行头
or drink fluoridated water.
或者喝含氟的水
You know what happens
你知道怎么了
if my mom uses a fabric softener?
假如我妈妈用织物软化剂
What?
怎么了？
I die.
我死了
Where are you?
你在哪里？
Over here.
这里
Where?
哪里？
By the skeleton.
在骷髅旁边
I got your message inside my cutlet.
我在肉排上看到了留言
I need to ask you something.
我要问你一些事情
What?
什么？
Do you believe in the existence of evil?
你相信邪恶的极限嘛？
Well, did you meet my mom?
那你见过我妈妈了？
My Uncle Fester's about to get married
我的叔叔要结婚了
to this woman in a white uniform.
跟一个穿着白套装的女人
A radiologist.
放射线研究员
A nanny.
一个保姆
I have to go to the wedding.
我必须要去婚礼
I have a pass. Want to come?
我有一张请柬，你要来嘛？
You mean like... on a date?
你的意思是……约会？
No.
不
I'd love to.
我很高兴能来
I,
我
Fester Addams,
do hereby declare my unending love.
我在此宣布我无尽的爱
I will worship you forever.
我会永远崇拜你
I will devote...
我将献出
my every waking moment
我醒着的每一刻
to your happiness alone.
为你的幸福
Oh.
Henceforth,I am your eternal
从今以后，我就是你的永远
and helpless slave.
和奴隶
Nice.
真好
Ditto.
同上
You're going to have a wonderful life together.
你们将会用美妙的一生
Yes, I am.
是的
Come, darling,
来吧亲爱的
let's see who's the next happy bride.
让我们看看谁是下一个幸福的新娘
Here, Debbie!
这里Debbie!
- To me!- Me!
我的！我的！
Oh, I have it!
哦，我拿到了！
- No! I have it!- It's mine!
不，是我的！我的！
Now you have to get married.
看来你的结婚了
It's not binding.
不是一定要遵守
Tramp.
浪费
- Bye!- Congratulations!
再见！恭喜！
- Congratulations!- Bon voyage!
恭喜！一路平安！
The key ingredient
关键的因素
to a successful
Hawaiian honeymoon
对一个成功的夏威夷蜜月来说
is romantic music.
是浪漫的音乐
[Romantic Music Plays]
I ordered this cassette from Time-Life.
我一辈子都准备这这盒磁带
5,000 of the World's Most Romantic Melodies.
5000首世界最浪漫的旋律
It's superb.
真好
What do you call this?
你叫它什么？
Number 438.
438号
So...
所以
do you like romantic living?
你喜欢浪漫生活嘛？
I do, so far.
是的，渴望很久了
I love romantic living.
我喜欢浪漫生活
Oh, Fester, how much do you love me?
Oh, Fester，你有多爱我？
With all my soul.
用我的整个灵魂
Would you do anything for me?
你会为我做一切嘛？
Anything.
任何事
Would you die for me?
你愿意为我死嘛？
Yes.
是的
Promise?
发誓？
Aah!
Aah aah!
Aah aah aah aah!
Pumpkin?
小南瓜
Muffin.
松饼
[TVPlays]
Darling, I know you're nervous.
亲爱的，我知道你很紧张
So am I.
是的
I'm not nervous.
我不紧张
I'm upset.
我慌乱
Because of the bathtub?
因为浴缸？
Th-Th--
That was an accident.
那是一个意外
I know.
我知道
I'm fine.
我很好
I know.
我知道
Don't give it another thought.
不要再想了
Don't be frightened.
不要在害怕
This is as new to me as it is to you.
这对你我来说都很新鲜
Have you really never had sex?
你真的从来没有做爱过？
Never.
没有
Then how do you know we're not having it right now?
你怎么知道我们现在没在做爱？
We'll be just like Gomez and Morticia.
我们像Gomez and Morticia
Pretend we're at home in my room--
假装我们在家在我的房间
Granny down the hallway,
奶奶在走廊上
Lurch by the door.
Lurch 看着门
Oh, my God.
哦，我的天
Please, what is it?
这是什么？
What do you need?
你要什么？
Only you, my dearest.
只有你，我亲爱的
Really?
真的？
Fester, I'm ready.
Fester，我准备好了
- Just one thing...- Gomez told me. No giggling.
-只有一件事……-Gomez告诉我不要傻笑
- And?- No hand puppets.
还有呢？-不玩手偶
- And...- What?
还有呢？-什么？
after we've made love,
我们做爱以后
you can never see your family again.
你不能再见你的家人
What?
什么？
Otherwise, I could never really enjoy myself.
否则我在也不会高兴
I could never give myself completely.
我在也不会满足
Unless I never see my family again?
除非我在也不见我的家人？
Yes. If I picture them in our lives,
是的，我想到他们
I could never achieve...you know.
我就不舒服，你知道……
Never?
永远？
Don't you love me?
你不爱我嘛？
Of course.
当然
Don't you want me?
你不需要我嘛？
Yes.
需要
Never.
永远不
Stud.
纽扣
Whoa!
Uh...
ahh...
It's so odd we haven't heard from Fester and Debbie.
真奇怪我们没有Fester和Debbie的消息
It's been almost a week.Hasn't it, little fellow?
一个星期了，那个小男人
Look at him.
看他
Too much fun at that reception.
非常快乐
here of the pup.
小东西
Excellent, Amanda!
完美Amanda!
Thank you.
谢谢
Next!
下一个
[Wednesday]
"Dear Wednesday and Pugsley,
亲爱的星期三和 Pugsley
"I love you dearly,
我爱你亲爱的
but I can never see you again."
但是我不能再见你们了
Glicker, go!
格雷格，射出去啊！
[Becky]
Good try!
很好
"When you are grown-up and very lonely,
等你们长大了很寂寞的时候
"you'll understand.
你们会明白
Love, Uncle Fester."
爱你们 叔叔Fester
He's a dead man.
他已经死了
Go!
射出去啊
It's an American bald eagle!
这是个美国秃鹫！
But aren't they extinct?
但是它们已经绝迹了啊?
They are now.
现在绝迹了
Mrs. Addams?
亚当斯夫人？
Yes?
恩？
Your hearse.Where's the body?
我看到您了，但是尸体呢？
Right there.
就那儿
But he's alive.
但他还活着
Tell me about it!
不要跟我说这个！
Fester, we may be together for a while...
Fester我们可能会在一起一会儿……
All our lives,cara mia.
我们的一生，我亲爱的
What?
什么？
Mon cher.
亲爱的
- Speak English.
- Pumpkin?
说英语
亲爱的？
If I have to be seen with you,we need to make some changes.
假如我必须被看到和你在一起，我们需要来点改变
Changes?
改变？
Be careful!It's a credenza!
小心点那是餐具橱
These are beautiful things.
这些漂亮的东西
They're from catalogues.
他们来自商品目录
Fester,get over here!
Fester到这里来！
It itches.
我长了疙瘩
Don't touch it,not until the scab falls off.
不要去碰它，不要等那疙瘩掉下来
Pumpkin, do you think these clothes are really me?
亲爱的，你认为这些衣服适合我吗？
Of course not.That's the point.
当然不是，这就是重点
- Where do you want this?
- The second floor boudoir.
您要把这个放在哪里?二楼边上
I'm her husband.
我是他丈夫
Fester!
Give me a kiss.
亲我一下
Give me a 20.Watch it!
给我20，小心！
That's a Queen Anne chandelier!
那是安皇后的枝形吊灯！
"Hawaii is wonderful.
夏威夷真美！
"I wish you were here,
我希望你在这里
"and I can never see you again!
我再也不能见到你了！
P.S., Debbie says hi."
附加，Debbie问好
I don't understand.For weeks not a word, and now this.
我不明白，一周杳无音信，现在就来了这个
Darling, come to bed.He can't be serious.
亲爱的睡觉吧，他不是认真的
Have I done something,said something?
我做了什么说了什么吗？
Why does my brother despise me?
为什么我的兄弟对我失望？
He adores you.
他崇拜你
I'd do anything for him.
我为他做了一切
At his request,I would rip out my eyes.
只要他愿意，我会摘掉自己的眼珠子
At his command,I would crawl on my belly
只要他要求，我会用肚子走路
through hot coals and broken glass.
上刀山下火海
Why wait?
那还等什么？
Has Fester gone mad?
Fester疯了吗？
This is all just some sort of phase.
那只是一些句子
Post-honeymoon malaise.
蜜月综合症
It's very common.
这很正常
Do you remember our honeymoon?
你记得我们的蜜月吗？
That glorious cruise.
那个豪华游轮
No quarrels.
没有争吵
No cares.
没有顾忌
No survivors.
没有生还者
Cara mia.
亲爱的
So...
那么
you still desire me after all these years?
许多年以后你依旧对我充满激情？
The old ball and chain?
我永远的爱人
Forever.
永远
I'll get them.
我明白
Heads up, campers.Thejamboree's only two weeks away.
听好了，队员们，离聚会只有两个星期了
And you know what that means--clean cabins.
你们知道那是什么意思--打扫小屋
Creating with clay and...
捏粘土
Canoes, canoes, canoes!
划船！划船！划船！
So we better get cracking, huh?
所以我们要分析一下
Look at this.I've got them.
看这个
Schizos and Serial Killers.
连环杀手
I have almost the whole series.
我有一整个系列
I'm only missing Jack the Ripper and that Zodiac guy.
我只错过了杰克和12宫杀手
But look.
但是看这个
"The Black Widow."
黑寡妇
It might be Debbie.
那应该是Debbie
At least three rich husbands...
三个富有的丈夫……
all dead.
都死了
I'll trade you.
跟你交易
For what?
交易什么？
Amy Fischer.
Each year，we conclude our summer
每年，我们总结我们的夏令营
with a very special presentation.
有些很特别的课程
Book, music,and lyrics by...
书，音乐，台词……
Gary Granger!
农夫克雷
And this year,
今年
the old bean has come up with something pretty exciting--
旧瓶装新酒
my own personal salute to the first Thanksgiving.
我向感恩节致敬
Now, we have thought long and hard
我们深思熟虑
about choosing just the right little actress
选择小演员
for the leading role of Sarah Miller,
主角Sarah Miller是，
our beautiful and kindly pilgrim lady,
我们美丽善良的圣女
and we have selected...
我们选择……
Amanda Buckman!
And in the roles of her pilgrim pals--
她神圣的好友是
Lily, Jennifer,
Tiffany, Missy,
Michelle, and Melissa!
But, of course,not everyone can be a star.
当然不是所有人都是明星
Let's not forget our cheery little Chippewas
我们不能忘记我们可爱的其他小队员
Mordecai, Yang,
Esther...
um...
Consuela, Irwin...
and, um...
I'm still not sure just how to pronounce this.
我到现在也不确定怎么发这个音
Jam-il?Jame-il?
[Gary]
Jamal.
Whatever.
随便……
And as their leader in the secondary
我们第二阵营的主角
but still compellingly written role of Pocahontas,
但是同样引人瞩目的 Pocahontas
guess who we have in mind.
猜猜我们选中谁
Our own little brunette outcast--
我们的名单
Wednesday Addams.
We want to see Debbie and Fester.
我们要见Debbie和Fester
Miss Debbie!
Debbie小姐！
[Debbie]
Debra!
Gomez...
where are we?
我们这是在哪里？
It looks familiar.
这里看起来很眼熟
Of course--the gates of hell.
当然--地狱之门
Welcome to my home.
欢迎来我家
Might we see my brother?
我们能看看我的兄弟吗？
No. He doesn't want to see any of you or that.
不，他不想看到你们或者这个东西
Why not?
为什么不？
Because he's in love.
因为他坠入了爱河
He's wrapped in a gossamer blanket of ecstasy,
他正裹在一条毯子里出神
and he hates your guts.
他恨你们
But why?
为什么？
Because you've flaunted yourselves,
因为你们炫耀自己
your great love affair.
你们的爱
You kept him a child.
你们把他当做小孩
I've made him a man.
我把他变成了男人
Let me hear this from his own lips.
让我听他亲口说出来
His lips are busy.
他的嘴很忙
You want to talk to these people?
你愿意跟这些人说话码？
Debbie.
Oh.
Go away!
走开！
That is not my brother.
这个不是我的兄弟
Sorry.
对不起
You have enslaved him.
你奴役了他
You have placed Fester
你把Fester
under some strange sexual spell.
置于性诱惑中
I respect that. But, please, may we see him?
我尊重这些，但是，请让我们看看他
Don't even think about it.
想都别想
You have gone too far.
你们走的太远了
You have married Fester.
你和Fester结婚了
You have destroyed his spirit.
你摧毁了他的灵魂
You have taken him from us.
你让他离开我们
All that I could forgive.
这些我都会忘记
But, Debbie...
但是，Debbie……
What?
什么？
Pastels?
Get out of my house!
滚出去！
Hit the road!
出去
And if you ever show your faces around here again,
你们要是再在这里出现
I'll have you locked up for trying to visit.
我就把你们锁在外面
Right, Fessie?
对吗？Fessie
Right!
对！
Luxor, nexor,burst, and burn!
（咒语）
What is she doing?
她在干嘛？
Just a curse.Have a nice day.
只是一个咒语，祝你愉快
I demand justice!
我要求公正！
Someone has married my brother.
有人跟我的兄弟结婚了
No.
不
She took him to Hawaii.
她把他带到夏威夷
They have moved into a large, expensive home
他们搬到一栋又大又贵的房子里
where they make love constantly.
他们在那里不停得做爱
I hate when that happens.
我讨厌这些
Arrest her at once without delay.
马上逮捕她
- Who?
- Debbie.
谁？
Debbie
My brother's wife, the temptress of Waikiki.
我兄弟的妻子，这个维基基海滩的女妖
Who are you?
你是谁？
What are you? Who moved the rock?
你们是谁？怎么回事？
Officer,you must issue a subpoena.
警官你必须开传票
I believe they own...
我相信他们有……
Gomez, no!
不！
A Buick!
一辆别克！
Just leave.Leave quietly. Leave now.
离开，快点离开，现在就离开
Don't make me call Ringling Brothers.
不要让我去叫人
Has the planet gone mad?
这群人疯了吗？
My brother... passion's hostage.
我兄弟被绑架了
I seek justice.
我寻求正义的帮助
Denied.
被否决了
I shall not submit.I shall conquer. I shall rise.
我要上报，我要斗争，我要起诉
My name is Gomez Addams, and I have seen evil!
我的名字是Gomez Addams，我看到了邪恶！
I have seen horror!
我看到了恐怖！
I have seen the unholy maggots
我看到了污秽的蛆
which feast in the dark recesses of the human soul!
feast在面对人类灵魂最黑暗的一面！
They're at camp.
他们在野营
I have seen all this,Officer.
我都看到了警官
But until today,
但是直到今天
I had never seen...
我从未见过……
you!
你这样的！
Hook him, book him,cook him. Now!
撵出去，马上！
Next in line.
下一位
Yes, I'd like to renew my passport, please.
我要更新我的护照
I'll be leaving the country very shortly.
我马上要离开这个国家
Traveling alone?
一个人旅行？
Yes. I'll be a widow.
是的，我就要变成寡妇了
~ Happy, happy turkey day ~
~ Hunger pains will go away ~
~ When you hear
the pilgrims say ~
~ It's happy turkey day ~
~ Happy, happy turkey day ~
~ Let's all eat
the Indian way ~
~ As Bastille
and Cape Cod day ~
~ On happy turkey day ~~
Look at you.Oh, Amanda, you look perfect!
瞧你，哦Amanda，你看起来真完美！
You're just the prettiest pilgrim I've ever seen!
你是我见过的最美丽的圣女！
Gar, come and take a look at this.
卡尔过来看看这个
Here they are!
他们在这里！
They were by the phone.
他们去打电话了
We were calling the FBI.
我们打给FBI
Their uncle's in trouble.
他们的叔叔有麻烦
You're late for your fittings.
你们排练迟到了
I don't want to be in the pageant.
我不想出现在舞台上
You won't help me realize my vision?
你不想帮我实现我的设想？
Your work is puerile and under-dramatized.
你的工作很幼稚缺乏表演技巧
You lack any sense of structure, character,
你缺乏对角色和结构的感觉
or the Aristotelian unities.
或者亚里士多德的了解
Young lady,I am getting just a tad tired
年轻的女士我只是在做一点尝试
of your attitude problem.
对于你的态度问题
Everyone, campers!
每一个人，队员们！
I have a wonderful idea.
我有一个好注意
Wednesday and Pugsley and young Mr. Glicker here,
Wednesday，Pugsley和年轻的Glicker先生在这里
well, they have just never quite latched on
他们不太理解
to the Chippewa spirit,
Chippewa精神
nor have some of their little comrades.
他们都没有朋友
Isn't that sad?
那不可悲吗？
- Yes!
对！
Don't we just hate that?
我们很讨厌这样对吗？
- Yes!
对！
Don't we wish they'd just die?
我们希望他们马上死掉对吗?
- Yes!
对！
We don't.
我们不
But you know what we'll do with them?
你们知道我们要对他们做什么？
We're going to make an example.
我们要做榜样
We are going to show that anyone,
我们要表示任何人
no matter how odd or pale or chubby,
无论多么古怪苍白或者肥胖
can still have a darn good time.
依然能享受快乐
Whether they like it or not.
无论他们喜不喜欢
What are you going to do?
你们要做什么？
Yes, indeedy, just the ticket.
是的，只是一张门票
Bambi.
小鹿斑比
Lassie Come Home.
灵犬莱西
The Little Mermaid.
小美人鱼
Stop it.
停下
He's only a child.
他只是个孩子
Don't worry.We're getting out of here.
别担心 我们会出去的
But...
但是
it's Disney.
那是迪士尼
Yes.
是的
~ The hillsare alive ~
~ With the sound of music ~
~ With songs they have sung ~
~ For a thousand years... ~~
~ And they knew that it was
much more than a hunch ~
~ That this group must
somehow form a family ~
~ That's the way we all
became the BradyBunch... ~~
~ You're always a day ~
~ A-way ~~
Well...
好……
good evening.
晚上好
Is there anything you'd like to say to everyone?
你们有什么要对大家说的吗？
Yes.
是
And just what might that be?
什么呢？
I'm not perky.
我不活泼
That's for damn sure.
非常
But I want to be.
但是我希望是
You do?
真的？
I want to smile
我想微笑
and sing and dance
唱歌跳舞
and be Pocahontas in Gary's vision.
像Gary设想的那样参演Pocahontas
Oh, darling,do you really mean it?
哦，亲爱的，你说的是真的？
Isn't she pretty?
她美吗？
She's scaring me!
她吓到我了！
Oh, Gar.
Yeah.
Aah!
Stay back!
退后！
He's very sick.
他病的很重
My baby!
我的宝贝！
Lumbar, dison...
（咒语）
pox and thither,
curad, brattle,
（咒语）
bone and brine!
Bone and brine!
（咒语）
Well, he's stubborn.
非常顽固的病
It works on cats.
这个咒语对猫有用
- What are we going to do?
- Is it hopeless?
我们应该做什么？
没有希望了吗？
Here it is.
在这里
"Chapter 18. Infant possessions."
18章婴儿着魔
He's possessed?
他着魔了？
"Warning signs--
症状警告
"severe alterations in appearance and personality.
人格和外貌的一些改变
Such alterations can become permanent."
这些改变是永久的
Permanent? Those golden curls?
永远？这些金发？
Those rosy cheeks?
这粉红的脸颊？
That smile?
这微笑？
"These terrifying changes
这些可怕的改变
"are most often the result of a troubled family life.
通常发生在家庭生活发生苦难的时候
Separations--"
骨肉分离
You mean...
你的意思是……
Fester!
Bingo! This kid knows
是的！这个孩子知道了
that something is not right around here.
这里有些事情不对劲
Unless Fester comes back, we're talking dimples.
除非Fester回来，否则我们有大麻烦了
Not in this house.
不会发生在这里
He could stay this way for years. Forever.
他会很多年这样，可能永远
He could become...
他会变成……
a lawyer...
一个律师……
I won't listen!
我不想听了！
An orthodontist...
牙科医生……
Mama, stop!
妈妈停下！
President.
总统
[Pubert Laughs]
Please! I beg you!
我求你了！
Take me!
带我走吧！
Each summer we take this occasion
每年夏天我们举办这个盛会
to celebrate a seminal event in American history.
来庆祝美国历史上一个重要的发展
This year, we depict
今年我们选择
perhaps the most important day in our shared past--
是我们以往分享的最重要的一天
the first Thanksgiving!
第一个感恩节！
A day for maize,
收获的一天
the Native American word for corn,
美国的粮食
a terrific turkey dinner,
美妙的火鸡晚餐
and brotherhood!
兄弟友情！
So, white meat and dark meat,
所以white meat和dark meat
take it away!
那走它！
~ Eat us, hey,
it's Thanksgiving day ~
~ Eat us,
we make a nice buffet ~
~ We lost the race
with Farmer Ed ~
~ Eat us 'cause
we're good and dead ~
~ White man or red man ~
~ From East, North,
or South ~
~ Chop off our legs ~
~ And put 'em
in your mouth ~
~ Eat me ~
~ Sauteed or barbecued ~
~ We once were pets,
but now we're food ~
~ We won't stay fresh
for very long ~
~ So eat us before
we finish this song ~
~ Eat us before
we finish this song ~~
Thank you.
谢谢
It was a senseless tragedy.
这是个意外的悲剧
Ha ha!
Angel, I'm going out for just a minute.
天使我要出去一会儿
I forgot the champagne.
我忘记了香槟
Our three-week anniversary!I'll go.
我们的三周结婚纪念！我走了
No, no.You're working hard enough.
不不，你做的够努力了
I'll just put your present on the table.
我把你的礼物放在桌子上
Don't peek!
不要打开
Oh, please, please!
求求你！
What is it?
是什么？
Is it string?
是串绳子吗？
You never know.
你永远都不会知道
Uh...is it a dog toy?
一个狗玩具？
Just you wait.
如你所愿
It's a bomb.
一个炸弹
What?
什么？
I know.Wait for my birthday.
我知道了。等我生日的时候拆开
Fester...
let me look at you.
让我看看你
I want to remember you just this way.
我要这样记住你
What do you mean?
你是什么意思啊？
Rich. Will you miss me?
富翁，你会想我吗？
But you'll be right back,won't you?
但是你不是马上就要回来吗？
Of course.
大然
Whoo!
Hoo hoo hoo hoo!
I am so glad we invited the Chippewas
我很高兴我们邀请了印第安人
to join us for this holiday meal.
享受我们的假期盛宴
Remember, these savages are our guests.
记住这些野人是我们的客人
We must not be surprised
我们不能太惊讶
at any of their strange customs.
无论他们的风俗多古怪
After all, they have not had our advantages,
毕竟他们没我们进步
such as fine schools,
例如好的学校
libraries full of books,
放满书的图书馆
shampoo.
香波
How. I am Pocahontas, a Chippewa maiden.
我是Pocahontas，一个印第安少女
An Indian.
一个印第安人
Enough said.
够了
And I am Running Bear,
我是Running Bear
betrothed to Pocahontas.
许配给了Pocahontas
In the play.
在这个剧里
20 grand for summer camp,
付给夏令营20000块
he's Mr. Woo-Woo.
他真厉害
We have brought a special gift for this holiday feast.
我们给今天的节日带来了特殊的礼物
I am a turkey. Kill me.
我是个火鸡，请杀了我
What a thoughtful gift!
多么好的礼物
Why, you are as civilized as we,
你们像我们一样文明
except we wear shoes and have last names.
除了我们穿鞋子还有有名字以外
Welcome to our table, our new primitive friends.
欢迎来我们的晚餐会，我们的新原始人朋友
Thank you,Sarah Miller.
谢谢你Sarah Miller
You're the most beautiful person I've ever seen.
你是我见过的最漂亮的人
Your hair is the color of the sun,
你的头发是太阳的颜色
your skin is like fresh milk,
你的皮肤像鲜奶
and everyone loves you.
每个人都爱你
Stop! Sit.
可以了请坐
Wait.
等下
What?
什么？
We cannot break bread with you.
我们不能跟你们分享面包
Huh? Becky, what's going on?
恩？Becky怎么回事？
[Becky]
Wednesday!
星期三！
You have taken the land
我们占领了陆地
which is rightfully ours.
我们这么做是正当的
Years from now,my people will be forced
很多年后，我的人民会被从这里赶出去
to live in mobile homes on reservations.
居无定所
Your people will wear cardigans
你们的人穿羊毛衫
and drink highballs.
和饮料
We will sell our bracelets by the roadsides.
我们会在路边卖我们的手镯
You will play golf
你们在打高尔夫
and enjoy hot hors d'oeuvres.
享受餐前热点
My people will have pain and degradation.
我的人民痛苦而退化
Your people will have stick shifts.
你们的人民会有汽车
The gods of my tribe have spoken.
我们部落的上帝说了
They have said, "Do not trust the pilgrims,
不要相信这些人
especially Sarah Miller."
特别是Sarah Miller
Gary, she's changing the words.
Gary她改词了
And for all these reasons,
基于以上原因
I have decided to scalp you
我决定剥下你的头皮作为战利品
and burn your village to the ground.
烧了你的村子
[Yelling Indian War Cry]
Aah!
Children! Campers!
孩子们！队员们！
Stop!You're destroying my text!
停下！你毁了我的剧本！
Aah! Aah!
He's not a team player.
他不懂团队合作
he,s only a child, but He needs friends.
他只是个孩子但是他需要朋友
He needs friends like this?
他需要这样的朋友？
- Aah!
- Oh!
Aah!
Uh, I beg your pardon.
我希望你再说一遍
Do something!
做点什么！
~ Macho, macho man ~
~ Feel my muscles ~
~ I've got to be a macho man ~
~ Mucho, mucho, macho, macho ~
~ I got to be a macho ~
~ Hey, hey, hey, hey ~
Hey! Wait!What time is it, Jorge?
等下！几点了！？
Ah, 6:25.
Oops. Got to go.
哦，我要走了
- No!
- Wait!
不！
等下！
Wait here.It's my anniversary.
今天是我的纪念日
I'll be right back.
我马上就回来
Your husband is a very lucky man.
你丈夫真是个幸运的人
Don't say that!
不要说这个！
~ Hey, hey, hey ~
~ Hey, macho, macho man ~
~ I got to be a macho man ~~
Cheers.
干杯
Oh, no, no.
哦不不
But, Officer...
但是警官……
my husband was in that house.
我丈夫在房子里
Happy anniversary, Debbie.
纪念日快乐Debbie.
Help. Help.
救命救命
Sweetheart! Did you get the champagne?
甜心！你买到香槟了吗？
Freeze!
不许动！
Pookie?
亲爱的？
I tried to make it look like an accident.
我想让它看起来像场意外
I tried to give you some dignity, but, oh, no, not you.
我试着给你点尊严，但是，不是你
What are you saying?
你在说什么？
I want you dead,and I want your money.
我要你死，我要你的钱
But--But...don't you love me?
但是--但是……你不爱我吗？
Is that a no?
不是吗？
Oh, do I love you.Look at yourself!
哦，我爱你，看看你自己！
You're a nightmare.You're the missing link.
你是个噩梦，你脑子里缺根筋
You shouldn't be married. You should be studied.
你不该结婚，你不该存在
You're a big,dumb, weird thing.
你是个又大又单调又怪的东西
No woman in her right mind could love you.
没有一个正常的女人会爱你
Yeow!
Thing!
东西！
I'll get you!And your little hand, too!
我会抓到你和你的小手！
Aah!
Come on.
来吧
No. I have to go back.For the others.
不，我要回去，去其他人那里
You're very brave.
你很勇敢
And to watch the place burn.You go.
去看那地方被烧掉，你走吧
Save your uncle.
救救你叔叔
I may never see you again.
我可能再也见不到你了
I know.
我知道
There are forces tearing us apart--
我们被迫分开
Gary, Debbie,seventh grade.
Gary, Debbie和七年级
I'll never forget you.
我永远不会忘记你
You won't?
你不会？
You're too weird.
你太怪了
We'll always have today and Chippewa.
我们共同拥有今天和 Chippewa
And this.
和这个
What is it?
这是什么？
Amanda's retainer.
Amanda的护圈
Cara mia.
亲爱的
Mon cher.
Come on!
来吧！
Move it!
走开！
Move out of the way!
"We looked,
（儿歌）
"then we saw him
step in on the mat.
（儿歌）
"We looked, and we saw him--
the cat in the hat."
（儿歌）
Are you enjoying this?
你喜欢这个吗？
To think...
想想
a child of mine.
我的孩子
"I know it is wet,
（儿歌）
"and the sun is not sunny,
"but we can have lots of good fun,
（儿歌）
that is funny."
Oh, no.
哦不
He lives.
他活下来了
Come on! It's Gomez!
快点！Gomez
~ Swing low ~
~ Sweet chariot ~
~ Coming for
to carry me home ~
~ Swing low ~~
My baby is ill,
我的宝贝病了
and my husband is dying.
我的丈夫就要死了
Oh, mama,what shall I do?
哦妈妈我该做什么？
Well, you have a black dress.
额，你有一条黑裙子
Gomez!
- Fester!
Fester? Where is Fester?
Fester？Fester在哪儿？
He's right here,mon cher.
他就在这里亲爱的
It's me, Gomez.
是我Gomez
I've tried to be someone I'm not.
我试着成为我不能成为的人
I live in shame...
我生活在羞愧中
and the suburbs!
濒临崩溃！
But you belong to Debbie.
但是你属于Debbie
You're Debbie's love toy.
你是Debbie的爱情玩具
You are Mr. Debbie!
你是Debbie先生
I am an Addams!
我是Addams
Fester!
Uncle Fester!
Fester叔叔！
Children!
孩子们！
You sent us to camp.
你把我们送去野营
They made us sing.
他们让我们唱歌
My own dear family.
我亲爱的家
How I've missed you all.
我多么想你
Our whole family--together at last.
我们一家终于在一起了
Three generations...
三代同堂……
above ground.
还没死的
In-laws!
还有姻亲！
I don't want to hurt anybody.
我不想伤害任何人
I don't enjoy hurting anybody.
我也不愿意伤害任何人
I don't like guns or bombs or electric chairs,
我不喜欢枪，炸弹或电椅
but sometimes people just won't listen,
但是有时候人们不听话
and so I have to use persuasion...
那我就必须说服他们
and slides.
用一些幻灯片
My parents--Sharon and Dave.
我的父母--Sharon和Dave
Generous, doting...
慷慨的，溺爱的
or were they?
真的吗？
All I ever wanted was a ballerina Barbie
我要的只是一个ballerina 芭比娃娃
in her pretty pink tutu.
穿着她的漂亮粉红短裙
My birthday.
我生日那天
I was 10,
我10岁
and do you know what they got me?
你知道他们给了我什么？
Malibu Barbie.
Malibu芭比娃娃
The nightmare.
一场噩梦
The nerve.
噩梦
That's not what I wanted.
那不是我要的
That's not who I was.
I was a ballerina--
我要的是ballerina
graceful, delicate.
华贵精美
They had to go.
他们必须死
My first husband, the heart surgeon.
我的第一个丈夫，心脏外科医生
All day long,coronaries, transplants.
整天冠状动脉和移植
What about your needs?
你需要什么?
"Sorry about dinner, Deb.
晚饭很对不起Deb
The pope has a cold."
教皇感冒了
An axe.
一个斧头
That takes me back.
让我想起了过去
Husband number two--the senator.
第二个丈夫--参议院
He loved his state.He loved his country.
他爱他的国家
What about Debbie?
但是Debbie呢？
"Sorry, Debbie.No Mercedes this year.
对不起Debbie今年买不了奔驰了
We have to set an example."
我们必须做个榜样
Oh, yeah? Set this!
是吗？就这样！
My latest husband.
我最后一个丈夫
My late husband Fester.
我现任丈夫Fester
The fool.
这个傻瓜
The corpse.
这个僵尸
And his adorable family.
和他可爱的一家
You took me in.You accepted me.
你们让我加入，你们接受了我
But did any of you love me?
但是你们爱我吗？
Really love me?
真的爱我吗？
Hands.
手
So I--I killed.
所以我杀人
So I maimed.
所以我分尸
So I destroyed one innocent life after another.
所以我毁灭一个又一个无辜的生命
Aren't I a human being?
我是人类吗？
Don't I yearn and...ache and shop?
难道我不可怜不痛苦，不应该购物吗？
Don't I deserve love...
难道我不渴望爱吗？
and jewelry?
和珠宝？
Adieu, mon cher.
再见亲爱的
Adios, cara mia.
Debbie, let them go.Take me and my money.
Debbie，让他们走，杀了我拿走我的钱
For what I've done,I deserve to die.
我该为我所做的去死
Sorry.
对不起
Goodbye, everybody.
大家再见
Wish me luck.
祝我好运
- Good luck.
好运
A birthday party!What a treat!
生日晚会！真好啊！
And to think I might have missed all this.
想想我可能错过这一切
What was I thinking of?
我在想什么？
Physical pleasure.
生理愉悦
Oh...
Uncle Fester,do you miss Debbie?
Fester叔叔，你还想念Debbie
Well, sometimes,late at night.
有时候，在晚上
I remember how she'd turn to me
我记得她怎么对待我
and say "Jesus, Fester,go back to your room."
耶稣啊Fester回你自己的房间去
Yoo-hoo!
Are we late?
我们迟到了吗？
[Chattering]
Not at all. We'rejust getting started.
没有，我们刚要开始
I hope no one minds.We brought along a guest.
我希望没人介意我带来了一个客人
This is our new nanny--Dementia.
这是我们的新保姆Dementia
Oh...
Dementia.
What a beautiful name.
多美的名字
It means insanity.
它的意思是精神错乱
My name's Fester.It means to rot.
我叫Fester，意思是腐烂
A toast.
土司
To the glorious mysteries of life.
为荣耀神秘的生命
To all that binds a family as one.
为所有像这样的家庭
To mirth, to merriment,to manslaughter.
为快乐愉悦和谋杀
- Hear, hear.
- [Chattering]
是啊是啊
To dear friends.
为亲爱的朋友
To new friends.
为新朋友
To youth.
为青春
How do I look?
我看起来怎么样
Disturbing.
乱七八糟
To passion.
为了激情
To paradise.
为了天堂
To pain.
为了痛苦
Tonight.
今晚
Ha ha! Make way for the birthday boy!
为生日男孩让路！
Thing, will you do the honors?
东西，你来完成这光荣的任务？
Your family is really interesting.
你们一家真有趣
Your parents are so involved with each other.
你的父母真爱对方
Wednesday, do you think,like, maybe someday
星期三，你想过没有，也许有一个人
you might want to get married and have kids?
你可能会跟他结婚并且生孩子
No.
不
But what if you met just the right man
但是假如你遇到了对的人
who worshipped and adored you,
崇拜你爱慕你
who'd do anything for you,
为你做任何事
who'd be your devoted slave?
心甘情愿做你的奴隶
What would you do?
你会怎么样？
I'd pity him.
怜悯他
Poor Debbie.She was sick.
可怜的Debbie，她真变态
She wasn't sick.
她不变态
She was sloppy.
她太草率
What do you mean?
这是什么意思？
If I wanted to kill my husband, I'd do it, and I wouldn't get caught.
假如我要杀我的丈夫，我会这么做，但我不会被抓住
How?
怎么办？
I'd scare him to death.
我把他吓死
No, you wouldn't.
不你不会
We're all very sorry, Debbie.
我们都很伤心Debbie
We wish you only the best.
祝你好运
Aah! Aah!
Aah!
~ Whoomp! Addams Family ~
~ There it is ~
~ Whoomp!
The Addams Family ~
~ Come on, come on ~
~ Whoomp! Addams Family ~
~ There it is ~
~ Whoomp!
The Addams Family ~
~ Yeah, yo, dig it ~
~ Back again,
the Addams Family ~
~ New baby in the house
makes three ~
~ Wednesday, Pugsley,
Lurch, you ring it ~
~ Fester, Grandmama,
and Thing ~
~ Wait, can't forget
cousin Itt ~
~ Tag team raps
another party hit ~
~ It's the Addams Family
movie thing ~
~ Gomez, Morticia,
come on, sing ~
~ Whoomp! Addams Family ~
~ There it is ~
~ Whoomp!
The Addams Family ~
~ Come on, come on ~
~ Whoomp! Addams Family ~
~ There it is ~
~ Whoomp!
The Addams Family ~
~ Let me tell you,
it's the A-D-D-A-M-S ~
~ The Addams Family,
y'all, yes, yes ~
~ They're creepy, kooky,
mysterious, spooky ~
~ As loony as can be
when you see the movie ~
~ It goes on and on,
the madness won't stop ~
~ Tick to the tock
around the clock ~
~ Tag team kicks the floor,
really, though ~
~ With the Addams Family,
so here we go ~
~ Whoomp! Addams Family ~
~ There it is ~
~ Whoomp!
The Addams Family ~
~ Hey, there it is ~
~ Whoomp! Addams Family ~
~ There it is ~
~ Whoomp!
The Addams Family ~
~ Come on, come on,
come on, come on ~
~ Whoomp! Family ~
~ Whoomp! Family, whoa ~
~ The Addams Family ~
~ Something's strange,
something's funny ~
~ Nanny's got a plot
to get the family money ~
~ Makes Fester
fall for her ~
~ Thing gets wise,
spreads the word ~
~ The family
comes to Fester's aid ~
~ The plot is foiled,
no one gets paid ~
~ It's the Addams Family
runnin' things ~
~ Get back
while tag team swings ~
~ Whoomp! Addams Family ~
~ There it is ~
~ Whoomp!
The Addams Family ~
~ Yeah, come on, come on ~
~ Whoomp! Addams Family ~
~ There it is ~
~ Whoomp!
The Addams Family ~
~ Yeah, give it to me ~
~ It's a family thing,
and it won't quit ~
~ They keep it together,
y'all, and that's it ~
~ They're not ordinary,
just strange ~
~ Some say loco,
insane to the brain ~
~ But you know
that you love 'em ~
~ In a class
by theirselves ~
~ None below,
none above 'em ~
~ It ain't nothing
to be ashamed of~
~ So give love to the folks
who go by the name of~
~ Whoomp! Addams Family ~
~ There it is ~
~ Whoomp!
The Addams Family ~
~ Yeah ~
~ Whoomp! Addams Family ~
~ There it is ~
~ Whoomp!
The Addams Family ~
~ Ooh-ee ~
~ The Addams Family Theme,
I'm gonna kick it ~
~ Step to the mic
like Cube and get with it ~
~ Props to the number one
family of horror ~
~ This song's for the movie
and the dance floor ~
~ Tag team
always delivers the funk ~
~ From the old school,
with the bump for the trunk ~
~ And it umps,
with big bass on the low ~
~ Like my homey all said ~
~ You don't hear me, though ~
~ Whoomp! Addams Family ~
~ There it is ~
~ Whoomp!
The Addams Family ~
~ Yeah, give it to me ~
~ Whoomp! Addams Family ~
~ There it is ~
~ Whoomp!
The Addams Family ~
~ Yeah ~
~ Whoomp! Addams Family ~
~ There it is ~
~ Whoomp!
The Addams Family ~~
~ Express yourself~
~ Ooh ~
~ You don't ever need
help from nobody else ~
~ All you've got to do
now, yeah ~
~ Come on ~
~ Express yourself,
come on ~
~ Let it out
of its creepy shell ~
~ Because
you know you could ~
~ Express yourself,
come on ~
~ Come on, people
Come on, people ~
~ 'Cause you know
it's good, yeah ~
~ Express yourself~~
~ Breaking hearts ~
~Just ain't my day ~
~ It ain't my day ~
~ All I want to do ~
~ Is love you ~
~ Well ~
~ Sugar, I won't fill ya ~
~ With regret, my love ~
~ Yo, what you're lookin' for ~
~ Is real lovin' ~
~ Real lovin' ~
~ No matter what you see ~
~ Is what you get ~
~ Ahh, baby ~
~ What you see ~
~ Yeah, is what you get ~
~ Is what you get ~
~ What you see ~
~ I said what you see ~
~ Is what you get, now, baby ~
~ Is what you get ~
~ And real ~
~ And the real thing ~
~ Is the best thing yet ~
~ The best thing yet ~
~ Oh ~
~ Oh, what you see ~
~ Yes, why ~
~ Is what you get ~
~ Oh, oh ~
~ You're so good ~
~ I can't stand myself~
~ Ah, ah, ah ~
~ Is what you get ~
~ Ooh, baby ~
~ What you see ~
~ Is what you get ~
~ I said what you see ~
~ Is what you get, now, baby ~
~ Is what you get ~
~ And real ~
~ Is the best thing yet ~
~ The best thing yet ~
~ Are you ready for me? ~
~ Whoo! ~~
~ Do it, do it any way
you wanna do it ~
~ Do it any way you wanna ~
~ I saw you ~
~ Do it any way
you wanna do it ~
~ Do it any way you wanna ~
~ I saw you, baby ~
~ Do it ~
~ Do it any way you wanna ~
~ Do it any way
you wanna, wanna, wanna ~~
~ Whoomp! Addams Family ~
~ There it is ~
~ Whoomp!
The Addams Family ~
The Addams Family ~~